want to see you don't buy looking for this strategy
and today is day four
and this hot samba that is really cool
it's super forward
it's pretty cool
I pack like this
only those who will enjoy
who doesn't get hurt when they drop
it's a subpoena
who's my name there
lady is being acted on for a sudden midday drop
during business hours
immediate execution is determined
the notification has a deadline of ten seconds
to acquire or consume
a unit of my paçoca
under penalty of continuing to have the same face as
until the end of the day
the regularization rate is two reais
we accept pix
to avoid your inflating prison
for lack of sense of humor
it's yourself
before is information
what way are you being acted
because it's from the energy search on time
determination
immediate power run during business hours
will want to regularize or will want to be arrested
I have ten seconds to purchase
and consume a unit of my paçoca
the regularization rate is two reais
we accept pix to avoid its fusion in flagrante delicto
for lack of humor
arrive there
we accept pizza too
okay after this son
okay,
I'm afraid of being arrested.
on sale
man you need to break the pattern
be more interesting than interesting
valeu
valeu bye
bye
tomorrow eight and a half in the morning
one more idea worth it
must have become
this agent in hand